

# **Aneta Texler**

Software Engineer with 3 years of backend development experience and 2 years of research experience in computer graphics. Although my primary interests lie in computer graphics / vision, mobile development, and data science, I am open to dive into varied computer science fields and technologies.



# **Experience**

Research Engineer, Czech Technical University in Prague 7/2019 - 2/2021

- Worked on several computer graphics research projects resulting in two publications.
- Developed a mobile application for Android allowing real-time style transfer to faces.
- Participated in writing technical papers.
- Hands on experience in C++, Java, Android, NDK, JNI, OpenCV.

Data Management Specialist, CRIF – Czech Credit Bureau

8/2016 – 6/2019

- Developed automated web scrapers for downloading pages and software for parsing HTML/XML/JSON/PDF files and importing the data into databases.
- Designed databases, scripted T-SQL queries and procedures.
- Maintenance and debugging of my projects and projects of others.
- Hands on experience in C#, .NET, HTTP, HTML, XML, DOM, XQuery, XPath, JSON, relational databases, Entity Framework, LINQ, T-SQL, SQL Server Management Studio.



# Selected Projects

FaceBlit [C++, Java] A research project dealing with style transfer from a static portrait to facial videos. My main contribution was a mobile application for Android that captures a face, stylizes each frame using a given style exemplar, and displays results, all in realtime. The UI is developed in Java and the style transfer logic in C++; connected via JNI.

StyleProp [C#, HLSL] A research project dealing with real-time style transfer from a 2D hand-drawn image to a 3D model. My main contribution was an upsampling method accelerated on a GPU that increased resolution and quality of the result.

Edge Detector [C++, CUDA] My coursework dealing with Canny algorithm to detect edges in images, accelerated by OpenACC and CUDA.

Web Applications [C#] Two different coursework projects, the first dealt with searching similar images based on their histograms, the second handled an e-cookbook (storing, searching, creating recipes). Hands on experience in ASP.NET Core, REST API, Entity Framework, LINQ, Razor, Angular.



# Education

MSc in Computer Science, Major in Data Science

9/2017 - 6/2019

Czech Technical University in Prague, Czechia

BSc in Computer Science, Major in Information Systems

9/2011 - 6/2017

Czech Technical University in Prague, Czechia



# Journal Publications

FaceBlit: Instant Real-time Example-based Style Transfer to Facial Videos I3D'21

A. Texler, O. Texler, M. Kučera, M. Chai, and D. Sýkora

In Proceedings of the ACM in Computer Graphics and Interactive Techniques, 4(1)

StyleProp: Real-time Example-based Stylization of 3D Models

PG'20+21

F. Hauptfleisch, O. Texler, A. Texler, J. Křivánek, and D. Sýkora

In Computer Graphics Forum, 39(7):575--586



# Personal Info



San Jose, CA



□ aneta.texler@gmail.com



650-670-0184



www.linkedin.com/in/aneta-texler



anetatexler.github.io



### C/C++

## Proficient

Algorithms, backend, Windows, Linux, Android native development

#### C#

## Proficient

.NET Framework

## Python

#### Advanced

Scikit-learn, Pandas, NumPy, Jupyter

#### Java

#### Advanced

Desktop and Android, NDK, JNI

#### Web

## Intermediate

ASP.NET Core, REST API, Bootstrap

# Computer Graphics / Vision

## Intermediate

Style transfer, face detection, image manipulation, OpenCV

### **Data Science**

## Advanced

Data pre-processing, data mining, web mining, machine learning

#### Database systems

#### Advanced

SQL, relational databases, object-relational mapping, Entity Framework, LINQ

## CPU & GPU Parallelism

#### Intermediate

OpenMP, MPI, OpenACC, CUDA

#### **Version Control**

# Advanced

Git, SVN